<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Denver Real Estate Podcast with Daniel Dixon</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Dixon Group - your professional Denver Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>The Dixon Group</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2022-03-08 14:44:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>The Dixon Group</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Denver, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Daniel@dgdenver.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>The Dixon Group</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>The Dixon Group</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Denver, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Denver Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Dixon Group - your professional Denver Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>SCALE Series, Part 3: Accountability</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/scale-series-part-3-accountability.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>The Dixon Group</author>
        <pubDate>2020-04-06 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/Recruiting/SCALE+Series%2C+Part+3-+Accountability.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Dan Brener, one of our top-producing agents, joined me today to discuss the &lsquo;A&rsquo; in our SCALE series: accountability.

Last time, we touched on accountability, explaining how we meet with all of our agents weekly to ensure they’re acting with purpose and efficiency.

Before he joined the Dixon Group, top producer Dan Brener worked as a solo agent. He didn’t have much structure in his life—he just rolled with the punches. Since joining us, however, he’s learned that when you attack each day and week with intention and hold yourself accountable, then you’ll start accomplishing the goals you’ve set for yourself, your clients, and your business

“We need to hold ourselves accountable for each day’s activities, so we can grow our business throughout the year.”

In this business, we usually don’t take days off because the work we put in today will pay off in a month or so. That means we need to hold ourselves accountable for each day’s activities, so we can grow our business throughout the year. If we can manage to hold ourselves accountable in all the right ways, that growth will also spill over into our personal lives.

If you have any questions about how to add accountability to your business and your life, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d be happy to schedule a quick, 15-minute call to help you develop your success.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/Recruiting/SCALE+Series%2C+Part+3-+Accountability.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/Recruiting/SCALE+Series%2C+Part+3-+Accountability.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Dan Brener, one of our top-producing agents, joined me today to discuss the ‘A’ in our SCALE series: accountability.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>The Dixon Group</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Dan Brener, one of our top-producing agents, joined me today to discuss the ‘A’ in our SCALE series: accountability.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Denver, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How We’re Creating a Seamless Experience</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-were-creating-a-seamless-experience.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>The Dixon Group</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-15 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/How+Were+Creating+a+Seamless+Experience.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Our goal is to create a seamless experience for you and your clients.

Our mission is to create a seamless experience for you and your clients to get your transactions clear to close within 15 days. We take pride in the trust that agents put in us to get their transactions to the closing table, and we promise to provide exceptional communication, unique problem-solving strategies, and education for your clients from application to after closing. We take the stress out of the transaction so you can focus on getting more business.

If you have any questions or want to know how we can help you and your business, feel free to reach out via phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/How+Were+Creating+a+Seamless+Experience.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/How+Were+Creating+a+Seamless+Experience.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our goal is to create a seamless experience for you and your clients.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>The Dixon Group</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our goal is to create a seamless experience for you and your clients.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Denver, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>SCALE Series, Part 2: Culture</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/scale-series-part-2-culture.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>The Dixon Group</author>
        <pubDate>2020-03-08 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/Recruiting/SCALE+Series%2C+Part+2-+Culture.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I&rsquo;ll discuss what the C in our SCALE series stands for: culture.

When you’re creating a culture in your business, do you want it to come by design or by default? We’ve been very intentional about maintaining our culture and who we bring into our world. So if you’re building your business team right now, or you’re just looking to add a transaction coordinator or lender, be sure that they mesh well with your business’ culture.

All of our agents are held to a very high standard of accountability, which is one of the most important staples of our culture. We’ve found that the top producing agents like this too; every week, they track their metrics and submit them to the team’s Slack channel on Sunday.

Not only do we have leadership accountability, but we also have team accountability. Each agent knows they’re reporting those metrics on Sunday evening for the whole team to see what they’ve accomplished.

Then, each Monday, we’ll do a quick one-on-one with each agent where we’ll review their pipelines, their Boomtown profiles, etc., and generally analyze what they’ve been doing over the past 30 days and how that has contributed to the current state of their business. We want them to have both intention and awareness behind their daily and weekly activities so that as we’re going over their quarterly and yearly progress, we have a clear understanding of their overall position.

“To maintain your culture, you have to be reminded of it every single day.”

The second aspect of culture to focus on is family environment. When you join the Dixon Group, we always joke that you become part of the family, but it’s true—when you create a partnership with someone, you need to have an emotional connection with them so that they know they’re supported and a part of the team. We’re a team of like-minded individuals with open minds, and all our agents embody the family mentality.

The last facet of culture is understanding your ‘why.’ Your whole team needs to understand your underlying motivation for what it is you do and how they contribute to it. When everyone’s on board, everyone has the same base motivations to do the best they can every single day.

The Dixon Group strives for culture by design. To maintain your culture, you have to be reminded of it every single day. If you don’t, yours will become a culture by default instead of by design.

Next time, we’ll discuss the A in SCALE: accountability. If you’d like more information about building a team or anything else to do with fostering a better real estate career, I highly recommend that you read “Great Teams: 16 Things High-Performing Organizations Do Differently” by Don Yager. If you’d like to talk about what you read or expanding your business in general, we’d love to be a resource for you. Feel free to reach out at any time.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/Recruiting/SCALE+Series%2C+Part+2-+Culture.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Dominique+Mathews/Videos/Recruiting/SCALE+Series%2C+Part+2-+Culture.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Today I’ll discuss what the C in our SCALE series stands for: culture.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>The Dixon Group</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Today I’ll discuss what the C in our SCALE series stands for: culture.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Denver, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>SCALE Series, Part 1: Strategy</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/scale-series-part-1-strategy.html</link>
        
        <author>The Dixon Group</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-20 11:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

A business is only as successful as the strategies behind it. Today in this first part of our new series, I’ll share a few of our business strategies as tips to help you increase your success.

Before each new year, we hold a 1-3-5 goal-setting session with each of our agents—if you’d like a template of these sessions, reach out to me and I’d be glad to send it to you so you can set up your own. In short, each agent sets one major goal with three objectives and five “hows” to achieve that goal. This is an incredible tool that allows each agent to have a vision for success in the coming year.

To parallel their 1-3-5s, we also do what we call a 411, where they each present their objectives for the month broken down into weeks. This allows them to track how many appointments they need to have with lenders and sellers.

“Tracking is a massive portion of our business plan.”

Speaking of tracking, we also make a point to track everything week after week so that our agents have a good grasp of where their business currently sits. That way, if they’re not on track, we can catch that before we get too far into the year. Tracking is a massive portion of our business plan; implementing a tracking system in your business will give you clarity and help you do what you need to do each day faster.

Our group’s theme is intentional living. One of the key pieces of living that theme is maintaining a work/life balance. We like to check in with each of our agents to find out how they’re doing in terms of their housing, family, interests, etc. They work hard every day, so we strategize to help them find a balance between their work and home life so they can continue to operate their business and enjoy life while they do it.

Next time in part two of our SCALE series we’ll talk about culture. If you have any questions in the meantime, don’t hesitate to reach out to the Dixon Group. We are here to be a resource for you.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>In part one of my new series, I’ll discuss business strategy and tactics you can use to strengthen your organization.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>The Dixon Group</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>In part one of my new series, I’ll discuss business strategy and tactics you can use to strengthen your organization.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Denver, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>We’re Teaching You Our Best Lessons</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/were-teaching-you-our-best-lessons.html</link>
        
        <author>The Dixon Group</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-07 15:51:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Daniel+Dixon/2020/Were+Teaching+You+Our+Best+Lessons.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I’m excited to announce the launch of our coaching and mentoring video blog. I jumped in to real estate in 2013 as a solo agent, and in just a few years, built a mega agent team, in-house mortgage team, ISA division, wholesale business, and ownership in a title company. There have been plenty of failures, lessons learned, and massive growth to get us where we are today and we’re excited to share all of that with you. We’ll bring you all of this information through our SCALE series, which stands for Strategy, Culture, Accountability, Leverage, and Experience.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Daniel+Dixon/2020/Were+Teaching+You+Our+Best+Lessons.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Daniel+Dixon/2020/Were+Teaching+You+Our+Best+Lessons.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’re teaching agents our most important lessons, the biggest mistakes to avoid, and more through our brand-new SCALE series. Here’s what you can expect from it.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>The Dixon Group</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’re teaching agents our most important lessons, the biggest mistakes to avoid, and more through our brand-new SCALE series. Here’s what you can expect from it.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Denver, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>The Dixon Group</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">The Dixon Group</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Dixon Group - your professional Denver Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
